好了  已经完成了
All right, you're done.
让我们看一下写好的代码
Let's take a look at the solution.
由于我们不能直接插入一个Vector对象
While we cannot insert a vector directly,
我们可以把Vector对象转换成数组
we can easily convert a vector to an array.
完成转换以后  bulkInsert方法可以实现高效的数据插入
Once we've done this, the bulk insert method will insert very efficiently.
看这里  我们放开了这些之前注释掉的代码
As you can see, we've uncommented out this next series of lines.
这些代码可以让我们测试一下
This allows us to test our output to make sure
是否向数据库中插入了正确的数据
that we've actually inserted the right thing into the database.
让我们运行一下应用
Let's actually run our app.
如你所见  我们将之前插入到数据库中的数据
And as you can see, we're actually reading the data out of the database
全部正确地读取了出来
that we just inserted all correctly.
现在我们的后台会高效地更新数据  我们确实需要
Now our back end will update efficiently, but we really need to be
在请求网络数据之前就可以查询本地的数据
querying things before requesting them from the internet.
总之  重点是设计一个响应式的应用
After all, the main point is to have a responsive application.
直到我们已经从网络请求到了数据以后
We're still not even updating the screen until we've
再更新屏幕
pulled data down from the web.
同时也要避免在UI线程查询数据
We also want to avoid doing our query on the UI thread,
因为在UI线程进行诸如查询数据库的操作会导致Android系统不能
because doing operations like queries on the UI thread cause Android to not be
足够快速地刷新屏幕  也就是帧抖动现象
able to draw frames fast enough, which introduces frame rate jitter.
好消息是  Android提供了一种叫装载器（Loader）的模式
Fortunately, Android offers a pattern for that known as Loaders.